Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- I.A.M., 1971-1995 (Box 133, Folder 9)
- Amalgamate Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Meat and Cannery Workers.. Etc., 1964-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Meat Cutters, 1959-1963 (Box 134, Folder 2)
- Meat Cutters, 1960-1964 (Box 134, Folder 3)
- Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Amalg., 1965-1969 (Box 134, Folder 4)
- Meat Cutters, 1970 (Box 134, Folder 5)
- Meat Cutters, 1970-1975 (Box 134, Folder 6)
- Mechanics Educational Society of America Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 135, Folder 1)
- Mechanics Educational Society '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 135, Folder 2)
- Mechanics Educational Society '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 135, Folder 3)
- Mechanics' Educational Society '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Merchant Marine '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 135, Folder 5)
- Metal Engravers and Marking '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 135, Folder 6)
- Metal Engravers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 135, Folder 7)
- Metal Engravers and Marking Device '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 135, Folder 8)
- Metal Polishers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 135, Folder 9)
- Metal Polishers, Buffers and Plat. '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 135, Folder 10)
- Metal Polishers. Buffers, Platers and Helpers International Union '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 135, Folder 11)
- Metal Polishers, 1960 (Box 135, Folder 12)
- Mine, Mill and Smelters '39-'44, 1939-1944 (Box 135, Folder 13)
- Mine, Mill '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 135, Folder 14)
- Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 135, Folder 15)
- United Mechanics, 1960 (Box 135, Folder 16)
- Mine, Mill and Smelters '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 136, Folder 1)
- Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers 1960-1967 (Box 136, Folder 2)
- Mine Workers, Progressive, 1940-1944 (Box 136, Folder 3)
- United Mine Workers of America '18-'50, 1918-1950 (Box 136, Folder 4)
- United Mine Workers of America, 1912-1944 (Box 136, Folder 5)
- Mine Workers, United '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 136, Folder 6)
- UMW 1950-54, 1950-1954 (Box 136, Folder 7)
- United Mine Workers of America '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 137, Folder 1)
- United Mine Workers of America '50-'55, 1950-1955 (Box 137, Folder 2)
- Mine Workers, United '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 137, Folder 3)
- United Mine Workers of America '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 137, Folder 4)
- United Mine Workers of America '18-'58, 1918-1958 (Box 137, Folder 5)
- UMW 1955-1959 (Box 137, Folder 6)
- United Mine Workers of America '55-'60, 1955-1960 (Box 138, Folder 1)
- United Mine Workers of America, 1950-1965 (Box 138, Folder 2)
- United Mine Workers of America '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 138, Folder 3)
- Mine Workers, United '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 138, Folder 4)
- Mine Workers, United '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 138, Folder 5)
- UMW '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 138, Folder 6)
- UMW 1960-1964 (Box 138, Folder 7)
- United Mine Workers of America '60-'69, 1960-1969 (Box 139, Folder 1)
- Mine Workers, United 1960-1964 (Box 139, Folder 2)
- United Mine Workers of America 1960-1964 (Box 139, Folder 3)
- American Federation of Musicians 1960-1964 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Musicians 1967- (Box 141, Folder 2)
- NLRB Union, 1969 (Box 141, Folder 3)
- National Treasury Employees Union w/ Development of Health and Human Services 1983 (Box 141, Folder 4)
- Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Agreements, 1999-2004 (Box 141, Folder 5)
- NCR Employees Independent Union (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Independent Employees Union of New Jersey, 1965-1968 (Box 141, Folder 7)
- United Neckwear Cutters, 1915-1934 (Box 141, Folder 8)
- New Jersey State Employees Assoc., 1985 (Box 141, Folder 9)
- Newspaper Guild. Amer. '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 141, Folder 10)
- Newspaper Guild, American Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 141, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Guild, Am. (CIO) '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 141, Folder 12)
- Newspaper Guild '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 142, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Guild '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 142, Folder 2)
- Newspaper Guild '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Guild '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Newspaper Guild '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 142, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Guild, American 1960-1964 (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Newspaper Guild 1965-1973 (Box 143, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Guild of New York, 1981-1983 (Box 143, Folder 2)
- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- Mail Deliverers' '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 143, Folder 4)
- Newspapers and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1963-1965 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Newspaper Deliverers of New York 1965-1969 (Box 143, Folder 6)
- Nurses Ass'n, American Int'l Printing Pressmen, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 7)
- NYS Association w/ The Mant Sinai Hospital, 1986-1989 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- NYS Nurses Association w/ Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center 1989-1991 (Box 143, Folder 9)
- NYS Nurses Association w/ Bionx-Lebanon Hospital Center 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 10)
- Office Employees International Union Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Office Employees '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 144, Folder 2)
- Office Employees '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 144, Folder 3)
- Office Employees '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 144, Folder 4)
- Office Employees '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 144, Folder 5)
- Office Employees '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Local 153 Office Employees Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Co. Inc., 1959 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- Office Employees' International Union Agreements A-G, 1956-1965 (Box 145, Folder 3)
- Office Employees Int'l Union, 1960 (Box 145, Folder 4)
- Office Employees Int'l Union 1965- (Box 146, Folder 1)
- Office Employees International Union, 1961-1964 (Box 146, Folder 2)
- Office Employees 1960-1964 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- Office Employees Int. (Box 146, Folder 4)
- Office and Professional Employees Int'l. Union (Box 146, Folder 5)
- Office and Professional Wkrs. Of Amer, United 1938-1939 (Box 146, Folder 6)
- Office and Professional Wkrs. Of Amer., United '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 146, Folder 7)
- Office and Professional Workers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 146, Folder 8)
- Office Professional '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 146, Folder 9)
- Office and Professional Workers. Of Amer. United Agreements 1965-1971 (Box 146, Folder 10)
- Oil, Chemical '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 147, Folder 1)
- Oil Workers, International '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 147, Folder 2)
- Oil Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1955-1961 (Box 147, Folder 3)
- Oil Workers, International '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 147, Folder 4)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 147, Folder 5)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Int. Union (Box 148, Folder 1)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 148, Folder 2)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 148, Folder 3)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers 1955-1959 (Box 148, Folder 4)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 148, Folder 5)
- Oil Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 148, Folder 6)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers 1960-1964 (Box 148, Folder 7)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers 1965-1969 (Box 148, Folder 8)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 149, Folder 1)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers 1960-1964 (Box 149, Folder 2)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 149, Folder 3)
- Oil Workers '65-'69, 1965-1969 (Box 149, Folder 4)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1970-1993 (Box 149, Folder 5)
- Oil Workers Int'l 1942-1951 (Box 149, Folder 6)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers 1970-, 1970-1988 (Box 149, Folder 7)
- Oil Field, Gas Well, 1935-1976 (Box 149, Folder 8)
- Flexible Packaging Workers at Amer., 1969 (Box 149, Folder 9)
- Packing House Workers, Nat'l Brotherhood 1956 (Box 149, Folder 10)
- Packinghouse Workers '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 150, Folder 1)
- Packinghouse Workers of America, United Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 150, Folder 2)
- Packing House Workers, United '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 150, Folder 3)
- Packinghouse, United '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 150, Folder 4)
- Packinghouse, Food and Allied Wkrs. 1960-1964 (Box 150, Folder 5)
- Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers 1960-1964 (Box 150, Folder 6)
- Packinghouse Workers, United (1965-1969) (Box 150, Folder 7)
- Painters and Allied Trades, Int'l. Bro. of., 1969-1972 (Box 150, Folder 8)
- Painters, Decorators and Paper Hangers, 1938 (Box 150, Folder 9)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of AM. Bro. of- Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 150, Folder 10)
- Painters, Decorators '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 150, Folder 11)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, 1955-1959 (Box 151, Folder 1)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, 1955-1959 (Box 151, Folder 2)
- Painters '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 151, Folder 3)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of Amer. - Agreements, 1961-1963 (Box 151, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, 1960-1964 (Box 151, Folder 5)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers 1960-1964 (Box 151, Folder 6)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers 1960-1964 (Box 151, Folder 7)
- Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers 1965-1969 (Box 152, Folder 1)
- Painters and Allied Trades 1971-1972 (Box 152, Folder 2)
- Paintmakers and Warehousemen's Union, 1962-1965 (Box 152, Folder 3)
- Paper, Novelty and Toy Workers '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 152, Folder 4)
- Papermakers, Int'l. Bro of Agreements '40-'49, 1940-1949 (Box 152, Folder 5)
- Papermakers, 1940-1949 (Box 152, Folder 6)
- Papermakers, 1950-1959 (Box 152, Folder 7)
- Papermakers, Int'l. Bro. 1955-1959 (Box 152, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1955-1959 (Box 152, Folder 9)
- Paper Makers and Paperworkers, 1955-1959 (Box 153, Folder 1)
- Paper Makers and Paperworkers, 1955-1960 (Box 153, Folder 2)
- Papermakers and Paperworkers, United 1955-1959 (Box 153, Folder 3)
- Paperworkers, 1960-1964 (Box 153, Folder 4)
- Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1960-1964 (Box 153, Folder 5)
- Paper Makers, 1960-1964 (Box 153, Folder 6)
- Paper Makers, 1963-1965 (Box 153, Folder 7)
- Paper Makers, 1964-1965 (Box 153, Folder 8)
- Paper Makers and Paperworkers United 1960-1964 (Box 153, Folder 9)
- Paper Makers, 1965-1969 (Box 154, Folder 1)
- Paper Makers, 1965-1969 (Box 154, Folder 2)
- Papermakers and Paperworkers, United 1965-, 1965-1969 (Box 154, Folder 3)
- Papermakers - 1970 (Box 154, Folder 4)
- Paperworkers Int'l. (Box 154, Folder 5)
- Paperworkers of America, United Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 154, Folder 6)
- Paper Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 154, Folder 7)
- Papermakers, 1955-1998 (Box 154, Folder 8)
- United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1958-1966 (Box 154, Folder 9)
- Pattern Makers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 155, Folder 1)
- Pattern Makers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 155, Folder 2)
- Pattern Makers League of North America 1960-1963 (Box 155, Folder 3)
- Paving Cutters '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 155, Folder 4)
- Petroleum Trades Employees Union, Inc., 1969 (Box 155, Folder 5)
- Photoengravers Union of N. Amer., Int'l. 1919-1944 Agreements (Box 155, Folder 6)
- Photo Engravers Union of North America International Agreements, 1960-1964 (Box 155, Folder 7)
- Photo-Engravers' Union of N.A. 1960-1965 (Box 155, Folder 8)
- Photo Engravers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 155, Folder 9)
- Photo Engravers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 155, Folder 10)
- Piano Workers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 155, Folder 11)
- Pilots Assn., Allied, 1965-1989 (Box 155, Folder 12)
- Plasterers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 155, Folder 13)
- Plasterers' '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 155, Folder 14)
- Plasterers' and Cement Masons' Operative 1960-1964 (Box 155, Folder 15)
- Plasterers' 1965-1969 (Box 155, Folder 16)
- Playthings, Jewelry and Novelty Workers Int'l. Union '45-'49 Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 155, Folder 17)
- Play things and Novelty Workers, 1948 (Box 155, Folder 18)
- Plaything, Jewelry '50-'55, 1950-1955 (Box 155, Folder 19)
- Plumbers and Steam fitters of the U.S. and Canada, United Assoc. of, 1957-1958 (Box 156, Folder 1)
- Plumbing and Pipes Fitting '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 156, Folder 2)
- Plumbing and Pipe Fitting '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 156, Folder 3)
- Plumbers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 156, Folder 4)
- Plumbing, 1955-1960 (Box 156, Folder 5)
- Plumbers, 1955-1960 (Box 156, Folder 6)
- Plumbers, 1955-1959 (Box 156, Folder 7)
- Plumbers, 1955-1959 (Box 156, Folder 8)
- Plumbing and Firefitting Industry, United Assn. OF Journeymen and Apprentices of the Agreements, 1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
- Plumbing, 1960-1965 (Box 156, Folder 10)
- Plumbing, 1955-1959 (Box 157, Folder 1)
- Plumbers 1965-1969 (Box 157, Folder 2)
- Plumbing and Pipe fitting 1970- (Box 157, Folder 3)
- United Association of Journeyman to Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry w. Public Service Electric and Gas Company 1982 (Box 157, Folder 4)
- Pocketbook Workers Union of WY, 1960-1964 (Box 157, Folder 5)
- Sleeping Car Porters, 1948-1954 (Box 157, Folder 6)
- Porters, Brotherhood of Sleeping Car, 1964 (Box 157, Folder 7)
- Postal Workers 1970- (Box 157, Folder 8)
- Potters, Operative 1907-1939 (Box 157, Folder 9)
- Potters '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 157, Folder 10)
- Potters '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 157, Folder 11)
- Potters '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 157, Folder 12)
- Potters '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 157, Folder 13)
- Potters, Nat'l. Brotherhood of Operative Agreements '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 157, Folder 14)
- Potters, Operative 1960-1968 (Box 157, Folder 15)
- Pottery and Allied Workers Int'l. Board, 1972-1975 (Box 157, Folder 16)
- Printing and Graphic Comm. Union, 1978 (Box 157, Folder 17)
- Printing Pressmen '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 157, Folder 18)
- Printing Pressmen '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 157, Folder 19)
- International Union of Police Association, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 1)
- Printers, 1955-1960 (Box 158, Folder 2)
- Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 158, Folder 3)
- Pressmen's, 1962 (Box 158, Folder 4)
- Printing, 1960-1964 (Box 158, Folder 5)
- Printing, 1960-1964 (Box 158, Folder 6)
- Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 158, Folder 7)
- Printing Pressmen 1965-1969 (Box 158, Folder 8)
- Public Employees Federation, 1978-1988 (Box 158, Folder 9)
- Public Workers of America, United Agreements, 1949 (Box 158, Folder 10)
- Public Workers of America, United Local 625 Agreements, 1946 (Box 158, Folder 11)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 158, Folder 12)
- Pulp, Sulphite '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 158, Folder 13)
- Pulp, Sulphite '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 158, Folder 14)
- Pulp, Sulphite '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 159, Folder 1)
- Printing Pressmen '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 159, Folder 2)
- Pulp, Sulphite Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 159, Folder 3)
- Pulp, Sulphite '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 159, Folder 4)
- Pulp, Sulphite '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 159, Folder 5)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper, 1956-1959 (Box 159, Folder 6)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Papers, 1955-1959 (Box 159, Folder 7)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Papers, 1960-1964 (Box 159, Folder 8)
- Labor Contract Local 299, 1962-1964 (Box 159, Folder 9)
- Pulp, Sulphite, Paper Makers, 1960-1964 (Box 159, Folder 10)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Workers, 1962-1964 (Box 160, Folder 1)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1954-1965 (Box 160, Folder 2)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 160, Folder 3)
- Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers 1965-1971 (Box 160, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, 1954 (Box 160, Folder 5)
- Radio Association 1948-1949 (Box 160, Folder 6)
- Radio Association, American '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 160, Folder 7)
- Radio Ass'n, American '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 160, Folder 8)
- Radio Assoc., American 1960-1964 (Box 160, Folder 9)
- Radio Communication Assemblers Union, Inc., 1967 (Box 160, Folder 10)
- Railroad Maintenance of Way, 1945 (Box 160, Folder 11)
- Railroad Signalmen '20-'44, 1920-1944 (Box 160, Folder 12)
- Railroad Signalmen '50-'60, 1950-1960 (Box 160, Folder 13)
- Railroad Signalmen, Brotherhood 1962-1965 (Box 160, Folder 14)
- Signalmen 1966-1971 (Box 160, Folder 15)
- Railroad Telegraphers, Order of 1940-1945 (Box 161, Folder 1)
- Railroad Telegraphers '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 161, Folder 2)
- Railroad Telegraphers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 161, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1952-1963 (Box 161, Folder 4)
- BRT 1944 (Box 161, Folder 5)
- Railway Yardmasters, N. Amer., 1924-1941 (Box 161, Folder 6)
- RR Yardmaster pre 1945 (Box 161, Folder 7)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 161, Folder 8)
- Railroad Yardmasters of Am. AFL, 1950-1954 (Box 161, Folder 9)
- Railroad Yardmasters of America (AFL-CIO) 1960-1963 (Box 161, Folder 10)
- Railroad Yardmasters of N.A. (Ind.) '44-'46, 1944-1946 (Box 161, Folder 11)
- Railroad Yardmasters, North America 1958-1969 (Box 161, Folder 12)
- Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks and 1970- (Box 161, Folder 13)
- Railway Carmen Pre-1950 (Box 161, Folder 14)
- Railway Carmen '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 161, Folder 15)
- Railway Carmen, Brotherhood 1957-1967 (Box 161, Folder 16)
- Railway Labor Executives, Assn. (1936-1951) (Box 161, Folder 17)
- Railway Labor Organization (1937-54), 1937-1954 (Box 161, Folder 18)
- Railway Patrolmen '44-'45, 1944-1945 (Box 161, Folder 19)
- Railway Clerks 1920-1939 (Box 162, Folder 1)
- Railway and Steamship Clerks '41-'44, 1941-1944 (Box 162, Folder 2)
- Railway and Steamship Clerks '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 162, Folder 3)
- Railway and Steamship Clerks '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 162, Folder 4)
- Railway and Steamship Clerks '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 162, Folder 5)
- Railway and Steamship Clerks 1960-1964 (Box 162, Folder 6)
- Railway and Steamship Clerks 1965-1967 (Box 162, Folder 7)
- Railway Supervisors 1940-1964 (Box 162, Folder 8)
- Agreements Railwaymen, National Union of, 1923 (Box 162, Folder 9)
- Retail Clerks 1939-1944 (Box 163, Folder 1)
- Retailer Clerks '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 163, Folder 2)
- Retail Clerks International, Ass'n., 1950-1954 (Box 163, Folder 3)
- Retail Clerks '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 163, Folder 4)
- Retail Clerks 1960- (Box 163, Folder 5)
- Retail Clerks Int'l. Union - Agreements Bx 155, 1976-1979 (Box 163, Folder 6)
- Retail, Wholesale Clerks '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 164, Folder 1)
- Retail, Wholesale '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 164, Folder 2)
- Retail, Wholesale Association of Ahoe Pattern Mfrs. Of Greater New York, Inc., 1950-1956 (Box 164, Folder 3)
- Retail Wholesale and Department Store Union (Box 164, Folder 4)
- Retail Wholesale '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 164, Folder 5)
- Retail, Wholesale '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 164, Folder 6)
- Retail Wholesale, 1955-1959 (Box 164, Folder 7)
- Retails Wholesale, 1955-1959 (Box 164, Folder 8)
- Retail Wholesale '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 164, Folder 9)
- Retail Wholesale '60-'65, 1960-1965 (Box 165, Folder 1)
- RWDSU '65-'70, 1965-1970 (Box 165, Folder 2)
- Retails Workers 1970-1975 (Box 165, Folder 3)
- Retail Wholesale, 1989-1998 (Box 165, Folder 4)
- Retail Wholesale, 1978 (Box 165, Folder 5)
- Retail Women's Apparel Employees Union, 1970 (Box 166, Folder 1)
- Roofers '45-'49 and 1935, 1935-1949 (Box 166, Folder 2)
- Roofers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 166, Folder 3)
- Roofers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 166, Folder 4)
- Roofers, Damp and Waterproof Workers, United Slate, Tile and Composition, 1960-1965 (Box 166, Folder 5)
- Roofers 1965-1967 (Box 166, Folder 6)
- Rubber '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 166, Folder 7)
- Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of Am. Agreements 1946-1949 (Box 166, Folder 8)
- Rubber Workers '40-'44 and 1937, 1937-1944 (Box 166, Folder 9)
- Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 166, Folder 10)
- Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, 1950-1955 (Box 166, Folder 11)
- Rubber, Cork, Linoleum (Box 166, Folder 12)
- Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, 1950-1955 (Box 166, Folder 13)
- Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, 1950-1955 (Box 166, Folder 14)
- Rubber Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 167, Folder 1)
- Rubber Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 167, Folder 2)
- Rubber Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 167, Folder 3)
- Rubber Workers '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 167, Folder 4)
- Rubber Workers '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 167, Folder 5)
- Rubber Workers 1955-1959 (Box 167, Folder 6)
- Rubber Workers '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 167, Folder 7)
- Rubber Workers '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 167, Folder 8)
- Rubber Workers '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 167, Folder 9)
- Rubber Workers '65-'69, 1965-1969 (Box 168, Folder 1)
- Rubber Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 168, Folder 2)
- Rubber Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 168, Folder 3)
- Rubber Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 168, Folder 4)
- Rubber Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 168, Folder 5)
- Rubbers Workers (1960-64) cont., 1960-1964 (Box 168, Folder 6)
- Rubber Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 168, Folder 7)
- Rubber Workers 1970-1979 (Box 169, Folder 1)
- Rubber Workers 1970-1979 (Box 169, Folder 2)
- Rubber Workers, United 1970-79, 1970-1979 (Box 169, Folder 3)
- Rubber Workers, 1970-1979 (Box 169, Folder 4)
- Rubber Workers, 1970-1979 (Box 169, Folder 5)
- Rubber Workers, 1970-1979 (Box 169, Folder 6)
- Rubber Workers 1975-1979 (Box 169, Folder 7)
- Rubber Workers 1980- (Box 169, Folder 8)
- National Federation of Salaried Unions, 1954 (Box 170, Folder 1)
- Sound, Gavel (Box 170, Folder 2)
- Screen Writers - Authors League, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 3)
- Seafarers '40-'49, 1940-1949 (Box 170, Folder 4)
- Seafarers Int'l. Union: Sailors' Union of Agreements '40'-'49, 1940-1949 (Box 170, Folder 5)
- Seafarers' '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 170, Folder 6)
- Seafarers' International, 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 7)
- Seafarers' Intn'l., 1955-1959 (Box 170, Folder 8)
- Seafarers' Int'l., 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 9)
- Seafarers' Int'l., 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 10)
- Seafarer's International Union '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 11)
- Seafarers' Int'l. (Box 170, Folder 12)
- Inland Boatmen's Union of the Pacific, 1939-1966 (Box 170, Folder 13)
- Marine, Cook and Stewards, 1920-1949 (Box 170, Folder 14)
- Marines, Cooks, Stewards '50-'55, 1950-1955 (Box 170, Folder 15)
- Marine Firemen '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 170, Folder 16)
- Staff Officers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 170, Folder 17)
- Service Employees International Union, 1987-1989 (Box 170, Folder 18)
- Service Station Employees 1960-1969 (Box 170, Folder 19)
- Service Employees International AFL-CIO, 1970-1991 (Box 170, Folder 20)
- Sheetmetal Workers Intn'l. Assn. Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 170, Folder 21)
- Sheet Metal Workers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 170, Folder 22)
- Sheet Metals '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 171, Folder 1)
- Sheet Metal Workers' Int'l. Assoc. '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 171, Folder 2)
- Sheet Metal Workers, 1960-1969 (Box 171, Folder 3)
- Sheet Metal Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 171, Folder 4)
- Sheet Metal Workers International 1965-1984 (Box 171, Folder 5)
- Shoe and Allied Craftsmen '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 171, Folder 6)
- Shoe and Allied Craftsmen '50-'59, 1950-1959 (Box 171, Folder 7)
- Shoe Workers Union, Children (1918-) (Box 171, Folder 8)
- Shoe Workers, '40-'44 CIO, 1940-1944 (Box 171, Folder 9)
- Shoe Workers, United '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 171, Folder 10)
- United Shoe Workers, 1947 (Box 171, Folder 11)
- Shoe, United '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 171, Folder 12)
- Shoe Workers of America, United Agreements '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 171, Folder 13)
- United Shoe Workers of America 1960-1964 (Box 171, Folder 14)
- United Shoe Workers of America, 1965-1969 (Box 171, Folder 15)
- Shoe Workers, Boots and 1941-1949 (Box 172, Folder 1)
- Shoe Workers, Boot and 1960-1965 (Box 172, Folder 2)
- Sleeping Car Porters Nat'l Brotherhood (Box 172, Folder 3)
- Stage '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 172, Folder 4)
- Stage Employees '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 172, Folder 5)
- Stage Employees, 1960-1964 (Box 172, Folder 6)
- Store Employees 1960-1965 (Box 172, Folder 7)
- Store Employees 1965-1969 (Box 172, Folder 8)
- Stage Employees 1970- (Box 172, Folder 9)
- State County '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 172, Folder 10)
- State County, Employees 1945-49, 1945-1949 (Box 172, Folder 11)